I will go over the register to get to me in my city council for Tuesday.
October 7, 2020.
Two, look at the Barnabrew old presentation.
It's the Mr. Glenn Pizz.
And I would like to read this box information before he does.
But I guess you can go on first.
No.
Question approved.
Take it.
He said.
Hi.
Michael.
Joe.
Barnes.
Hi.
I'll read this.
Proclamation.
Clare.
Declare.
The clarification of.
October 7, 2020.
Bob has.
Glenn.
Pizz.
Day.
In the city of.
Michael.
being recognized for his distinguished and significant contributions.
Now, whereas Glenn Pitz, Glenn Pitz was born in 1925, and raised in the area, and made
my own and his home, he had listened to the U.S. Navy during World War II, and whereas
Glenn Pitz served on the U.S. Navy ship, the U.S.S. McIntylen, as an amphib, known now known
as the Navy Seals, during World War II, with a mission to protect beaches in the Pacific.
Pitz was tasked with either driving under enemy fire to disconnect and detonate mines at
great peril.
Often under heavy fire from enemy forces, the U.S. McIntylen miraculously sustained little
damage, and whereas Glenn Pitz continued his Navy service on the U.S. McIntylen as
the conclusion that the conclusion of World War II, to return on the U.S. to the United
States.
And whereas Glenn Pitz served for many years on the American Legion's post, 147 military
funeral day-to-day death detail to honor our country's veterans, and whereas Glenn Pitz served
as a founder and creator of the American Legion post, 147 military museum to remember and honor
the service of U.S. veterans and serve as a place for keeping historical records and artifacts
and to foster knowledge for all generations, and whereas today his Glenn Pitz, 100 per day,
and he is an honorable and valued member of our community.
Now therefore, may resolve the mayor's blessed partner in my Amositi Council, due here by the
player Tuesday, October 7, 2025, as Glenn Pitz date with him in the city of Miami.
And witness therefore, I have run to you, sir.
My name with the seal on this day, October 7th of our Lord, 2025.
Three public input scheduled personal transfers.
We have one, Mr. John Terry, with idea tech.
Thank you.
Even in council, I'm recognizing a few faces in here,
but for those who don't recognize me and haven't met me.
I'm John Terry with idea tech.
We are a fiber optic internet provider.
We've been communicating with the city for a couple of months here.
And I would just like to publicly apologize to Tyler,
Blast and Derek, who have annoyed over the past few days
trying to clarify some internal communication issues on our end.
We thought we were going to be on the agenda tonight.
It was clearly communicated that we were not.
And so we are on the agenda two weeks from now.
And I'm looking forward to coming in and visiting with you guys
and telling you a little bit more about myself and who we are.
Thank you.
For presentations and discussions,
with outside organizations,
hey, update regarding the streets and population,
and possible purchase of the world and Mr. Rick Baldritch.
Even you guys, I would be remiss before I even begin this to
let you guys know you just participated in once at a lifetime event in all honesty.
And it told everybody that could today,
Glenn donated a pocket knife that he found.
We landed on Eojima and you donated that today to the military museum with there
Rusted and as you can imagine
We also had a talk about that imagine that pocket in that guitar
That's an amazing event that a lot of people can get to see today, so
Anyway, thank you for allowing me some time to come in and talk about our street citizens
As most of you know, this has been a near and dear project for me for quite a few years
We do have a
significant increase in people that are here in Miami that
Most of them made themselves home, some of them are just transitting through
We constantly try to stay updated on everybody that comes in the town
I've got some, but I'll consider trusted agents out there on the streets
That keep us informed whenever they find new people
If there's trouble, whatever the case may be
And this week alone, here we are, what is it Tuesday?
We counted 32 new people today, alone, that we have not seen in the city before
Last Saturday, our last Saturday the month we do a feed forum
We had 47 folks show up, five of which were familiar faces
So that just tells you, we've got a, we've got an issue with the folks coming in
We know and we've reported you before that
Tulsa crisis center has been sending people here, they drive them up here
And we know the job employees department is brought people over
So, is it going to end?
Well, I would certainly hope so
But with everything that's transitioning and Tulsa right now, we expect to see a lot more people
Hit this way
The general indication that we give when we talk to people when they're brought up here is that
People are telling that Miami has all the resources you need
Far more than what we have, and that's Tulsa and Jonathan
We really don't have much of anything
So, we are trying to maintain as much contact with the folks on the street as we can
Certainly trying to keep them on a trouble
We kind of lumped them in the different groups, if you may
We kind of sort of know what part of town are we call them, our bicycle berate, Berge, the midnight writers there
We kind of have an idea what they are, what they hang out and what places they are staying
And when we take it all the way down from our very strong mentally ill folks on the street, which there is a lot of them
Down to the folks that are just there more comfortable living on the street, because they have no obligations, no bills
And they know where to eat, they know where to get clean, they are not trouble makers
In fact, most of them belong to a work party that we have
If we know we have got people out there that need a long cut or damage picked up, what other case may be, we just have to get them there and they go out there and do the work
So, we are working hard with our folks within the city, especially folks that have been here for a while
To try to get them back on their feet, a lot of them are just
people that fell and nobody was there to pick them up in everybody.
Everybody in his rooms to pay days away from whining on the street when you think about it.
We have been very successful at our shelter we had in January and February of the 50
something people that we had sheltered in the hundreds of people that came through to eat and
things.
We have six of them that have full-time jobs.
We have two couples that were able to get housing for.
We have two people that had absolutely zero identity whatsoever.
We were able to work with their home state, birth certificates and things like that to
get them ID cards and one that even got a driver's license now.
We're working very hard to try to help the folks as much as we can.
As you know, Miami has been without a shelter for quite a few years.
It's kind of been my personal goal to wind up with something in this town that we could use
as a facility for our folks on the street.
We have been blessed with the possibility of the best part about this is the church.
It's a church that's been closed down for a while.
It's the northwest of some of the God church for those that are familiar with that area.
We are potentially very close to getting that building purchased.
And when that building's purchased, I want to stress it will not be a shelter for insurance purposes.
But we can use it as a cooling station and a warming station in the winter time.
So people might have to spend the night there, but it is not a shelter.
What's up?
I know you're going to ask me that and I forgot to bring with me.
Yeah, I think it's between C and D up there on the right side for anyway.
It's northwest of some of the of God.
And the only question that's kind of lingering out there now is is there any issues with the city
of that being purchased and moved forward as a facility that we can work with our folks on the street.
We have a lot of plans for it.
We'll have a kitchen in it.
We will serve meals out of there.
Of course, we will have a food bank but that food bank is going to be on like most other food banks.
And that we are going to deal with strictly fresh meat and fresh produce something that folks just aren't getting.
Any of the food banks are able to provide meat and fresh vegetables and things like that.
So we're going to focus on at least food like food bank wise, which means we'll also be helping the families that are in the county that have a lot of food
and security problems.
And we have a lot.
So it's going to be a multifaceted facility.
We believe that with a model that we used the last two shelters in particular and how we address with these people and how we work with these people.
We think it will be very successful and we're looking forward to even have more perhaps working for the city someday.
Anybody have any questions from the council or anything I may answer?
What's our, what do you think our number or population is in the street so it's in here?
We're just over 200.
I know that sounds like it's extreme, but we've counted.
It knows the faces that we've been able to put hand while I won't say hands on.
We've been able to see.
We've gone by the houses where people are.
We've gone by the camps where people are.
And in our folks that are, like I said, our trusted folks at Ronda Street
have been able to give us a list by name of a lot of the folks that have given it down.
And now it's starting to spread outside the city.
I got contacted this weekend by pay-setter church.
There was somebody camped out underneath the water tower out there.
And he in turn said, oh yeah, there's a lot of people out there.
There was there too if you want to know.
So we're starting to get an awful lot of people here.
And of course there's to call whether it starts settling in.
They're not going to want to travel much more.
So they're going to look for a place to get warm for the winter.
So what efforts do we have in place to help them be reconnected with their home states?
With their home states?
Yeah.
We do everything we can to work with them to find out where they're from.
Right.
We provide a bus tickets.
If we've got the funding, we'll provide a bus tickets there.
We've sent out six in the last several months.
And some of them just they don't want to go back here for a lot of reasons.
And the other other interesting thing about it once we can find out who they are.
We will try to do a background check on them as well to make sure that they are not.
You know, sex offenders or things like that that we just can't.
There's nothing we can do with we can't break them into facility and depending on where they are and things like that.
So we try to do as much as we can that help people.
Some folks just don't want it.
We get it.
But yeah.
It just seems to be we're providing them so many different entities, food, shelter, things like that.
You know, what are we doing to get them that comfort?
Because I wouldn't want to leave you there if you're providing everything for me.
I agree.
We we're doing everything we can to prevent the handouts.
We'd rather call it a hand up.
And that's why we've started the work party for one where if they want food or if we cook at the end of the month.
Or we help them in the other way and then we tell okay, here's a deal.
Show up and we'll take care of which you're going to do this.
We do have like I said, the bicycle brigade that.
Not much we can do about those.
People I guess I'll clarify I'm asked.
We have options we'd like to do but we just can't do that.
In our panhandlers, I will say this a couple folks that are in town and handling.
They live pretty well as we found out.
You'll find most of our people that live here on the street or not panhandling. They're not
big in for food or anything like that. We do have a couple that are currently living out of the dumpsters
We know who they are
And we're trying to
Trying to get him away from that routine
So if you go to McDonald's and other places to see him out there pizza
We know who they are and we're trying to work with them. We try to get a person that happens if we get him
We make an appointment with a gran lake. We get him evaluated by gran lake and then if grand lake
Teams necessary they will get them their appointments look at them their Medicaid get him on medication get him on those things
And then we start working with like
Where's home?
It's kind of like dealing with a lot of folks that are
Addicts they're not very forthcoming with information
So it's a sit down and talk for a few hours before we get
Accurate information out of them. So it's sometimes a game. It could be a fun game
Ask a million questions out of them, but we try to do everything for a my hand up perspective
The handout just don't work. We've got folks that if we get him cleaned up they're willing to cook
You know that they're willing to do things and our building for example when we had the shelter
They had chores. They had things to do it out in the shoveled sidewalks in the winter for people
So that they understand
You know it's not a handout. They know me
So so do you guys collaborate with any local businesses to get them set up the jobs so they can start earning them
Well, yeah, yeah, in fact, you know places like Jan and Farms have worked with us for years
They're ready to hire anybody feel they'll hire anybody that we bring them
Discovery plastics have done in great service solutions this past winter hired
I think it was a plumber or electrician that we had in there that again just fell on our times
He got hired
So we work with all the businesses that we can to try to get him into place
I think probably a just one real quick very success story a very huge success story
When we had the shelter set up at first Christian church a few years ago because of flooding
We had a young man in there that sometimes you sit and watch and it was amazing
He was amazing with the kids. He was amazing. He was always tinkering with something
And I sat down and talked with him for quite a while
He just didn't seem like he's the type person that would you know, you would see traditionally on the street
He admitted he just fell nobody'd pick him up. So he just kind of that's what happened to him
And I went over to see if I made Chuck Stots and
hired him on the spot hired him no identification nothing and he took a chance on the guy and he was still working there right up to him Chuck asked
So that's just that's what we do for people
Got a little bus one
be questions. So one thing we hear a lot is if you build it don't come
So if you get this facility, what's going to do?
more people like Job and PD or Charles Christ Center or more people from
Governor and Governor and Governor people off in our population term from 200 to
500. Right, you know, the interesting I had a meeting with Ben Loring of the
Danies, so why don't we just call the mayor of Tulsa? That's easy to do, but I guarantee
he probably even know what's going on. I bet you he don't know what's going on.
I'd like to achieve a place on these other towns, probably already know about it.
Oh yeah, I think, you know, and it needs to be done.
Can we prevent anybody from coming? Probably can't, especially with Tulsa right now
at all this mass stuff that's going on there. They got to move and in the next
logical place form, according to them, it's also crisis center as well.
We'll take them to Miami. They have everything.
Of course, when they get here they find out there's just horrible.
I mean, I go to the federal building all the time and Tulsa, and it's, I mean, there's
thousands of them living on a street there right around the federal building.
It's insane.
All the respects, not Rick's, possibly.
We'll go back to that.
All the great.
Yeah, and yeah, and I had some great meetings this week with folks from Oklahoma City.
Some of our legislators and things about, they're asking the same question, what can we do to stop
and prevent this? Well, you know, give me the money that Tulsa got this year for the homeless
program. They got $18 million and where's it spent?
I'd like to know, show me where they spent it, and then give me $1 million.
And I can show you what we can do.
And we'll, I mean, the homeless situation has been around since Manwalkers.
Well, that's good point. They're going to ship them over here.
Exactly.
I'm going to have a problem right now.
The ordinance, the order to bring that in.
I agree.
If they're going to ship them here, but the big thing is we want to, if we can rehabilitate them
and get them back up and working or whatever the case be with their situation is,
whether it's rehab or get them into someplace like that, we are working very hard
at trying to get the state to look at very hard the mental health issue and a mental health
facility again, somewhere where people can be cared for on the streets just not here.
So we'll work with Grand Lake, very close, and we do get a lot of people that we have.
Do they stay? That might be a different story.
But the big thing is we're getting them there, and at least for those that do stay, they're doing very well.
I don't know if anybody's familiar with TK.
I'm not going to use this last name because he's been around here.
Very long time.
We sent him over four years to rehab four times.
In January when I had him, we talked for hours every day.
What God was going to do for him.
He called me from Texas two months after he got out of the shelter.
He said, I need to go out and I need to go now.
What's the difference he said?
You woke me up.
TJ took a bus back from Texas two.
to Joplin and drove directly past by him without looking, smelling or tasting anything here.
Called me every day from Vanita, called me every single day from Tulsa and where he went to rehab.
He told me, God doesn't have his hand in these things. He called me every day at 6 o'clock.
One day called me at 12 o'clock.
Oh my God.
But he said, you never guess what happens today, I was like, yeah, probably not.
He said, I'm sitting there having dinner in my wife walked in.
I was like, what's back up a few years?
What were you married?
He said, quite a few years ago, and we just didn't work as we were both.
The way we were.
She walked in that cafeteria that day when he was having lunch.
They're still together, still moving forward, apartment, living life, and it's also just grand.
It'll work.
We're going to work.
We just like to get the opportunity to do it.
On the 200, we have currently, how many of those are single people?
How many of those are family units?
We've got eight, I'll say, families. We've got eight couples that we know of.
Most of them are singles.
And the other thing that's kind of underving is we're starting to see a spike in a lot of the females that are on the street.
Typically, they're very resilient. They can find a place to put their head to the night.
You know, somebody's couch with the case may be, but we have an awful lot of females out there right now that are just camping out.
Pizza, I drove by pizza hut, saw something peculiar, pulled a parking lot.
They're two young ladies there that we have never seen before.
That's what they're doing is sitting outside pizza hut and people come out or give them a pizza to eat.
But they're definitely, they're definitely newbies in town, and you know, just looking for something to eat.
And a place to put their head.
But eight, yeah, we got eight couples. I'll put it.
But it's family.
We've not come across any children, thankfully, right now.
And I don't know, maybe my own public schools has a better feed on.
The number of kids that we have that are couch hopping and things.
We have not seen them on the street, which is a good thing.
Last year we'd find them, you know, just like everybody else in storage sheds or people's backyard sheds and
upstairs living and things like that.
So I'm sure the joke and probably time in on that a lot better.
I can write that.
Yeah, we're trying to work with each of the school districts to get a range, get a number.
But like I said, we have not, we have not had any that we have seen that have been on the street.
We know they're there.
That's actually insane.
We've got to do something with that.
With the kids.
They can't be.
And it's snowballs in there because food.
And then sure they get something from the food bank.
It may not be as nutritious that in the backpack program.
You know, which are mainly snacks for the weekend.
It might be the whole family for the weekend.
But it's still not very nutritious.
So it kind of snowballs.
A lot of people try to do things.
But getting things out there like the meat.
Fresh produce and things like that.
You know, getting a hot meal prepared three times a day.
So that they can get something insecurity.
Food insecurity folks, especially.
It's not going to be just for the our folks on the street.
But those that need a meal.
And take on some meat and fresh vegetables and things.
The other question for Rick.
Just one.
Rick.
First of all, thank you for everything you do.
You're a valuable member of our society.
The question I would have is.
Have you done any neighborhood chemistry in this area where you're looking at this facility?
And question the neighbors about having something like this in their neighborhood.
I mean, because that's the kind of questions as councilman we're going to get.
So I'm just curious what if any feedback you've gotten in that realm.
Folks that we've been able to find outside.
We've got to just ask them to say, hey,
what do you think?
As he was, if on some folks kind of like, well, you may have to see how it went.
And it's not going to bring the bad people in our neighborhood.
Of course we don't know that.
But we have got through some of the neighborhood there.
We haven't got on every door.
I know it means we could do a canvas easy to make sure we get not only the block to church.
It's on but in a sit right on a corner so we can attack that area.
Pretty easy.
The church, the assembly of God, in the northeastern here, the folks that have the, that
are going to be selling it, have actually come forward and said that they've Dr.
people there, or long time members of the Old Assembly, and they have plotted.
In fact, there's three other organizations that are looking at that church, and they've
all told them that the assembly is told them that they need to be in another assembly function
in each church.
And they know ours as a minute, I have two pastors, I have a Baptist pastor in a assembly
pastor, I'm going to be on staff, and in fact, the sanctuary that church brings is going
to be left as it is.
It's going to be a ministry, it's not just going to be a place for them to get free meal
and things like that.
They're going to be a minister too, they're going to be talk to you, they're going to be a
It's just a high volume area already, folks that folks there haven't seen them want to make sure everybody's coming.
All right.
Thank you, Rick.
Thank you.
I'll be coming by on the school, public school, bond proposal.
Thank you very much for having me here this evening.
I'm so excited to be able to visit with you about our upcoming bond proposal.
The vote will be held on October 14, but we'll just kind of get started.
All right.
So this year in our school district, we have established this thing together.
Because it's very important for us that we're not just focusing on one person trying to make change.
It's going to take everyone working together to make change.
That doesn't happen just within the school district.
That happens within our community as well.
So that's why it's very important that we're coming together and we're thinking about how can we improve the future for our students.
So this is something that's been very near and dear to me this year.
And I think that we've seen stronger connections, not just in the district, but also throughout the community.
I think if any of you came to our homecoming a parade last week, we had a huge turnout.
And I think that just speaks to the volumes of people that are getting engaged and are excited to be part of our district.
So this is what's leading us this year together.
How do we continue that work together?
So this last spring we came together and we started identifying what did we want to focus on, not just in this school year, but in the school year to come.
And one of those main things is the facilities and bond issue.
So our focus areas, we're improving that facility needs for growth.
So we are seeing that we're getting more students and we will be able to provide students with opportunities within the facilities that we have currently.
Developing that bond campaign.
So we work as a committee to develop how are we going to publicize this for our community.
So they have all the information and then creating a long term facility master plan.
I laugh whenever I talk about this because we get all of this information together and then when you're looking at the plan it's going all the way to the year 2040.
And you think that seems like it's going to take forever to be here, but really it will be here in the blink of an eye.
So how do we work together to make sure that we're meeting those goals?
So here's a little bit about our long term facilities plan.
We've centered this on three things.
The first is growth, safety and then innovation because we have to be ready for as our community grows.
We have to make safety a number one priority for our kids if they're at school they need to be safe while they're there.
And then how do we develop that innovation?
We want kids to choose my own public.
is the place that they want to be providing those opportunities.
So these are the three things that we're focusing on as we're developing that long term
plan.
Some commitments that we've made, we want to make sure that we have those safe learning environments
and that we're efficiently using our resources.
It's not just about what's going to fix the problem in this minute, it's what's going to fix
the problem for the future.
And then having those modern and flexible spaces for learning, along with developing that financial
responsibility.
Because we're utilizing taxpayer dollars to be able to make these things happen, we need
to be able to account for where that money is going to go and how it's going to be used
for future commitments.
So here's that 24-year goal.
The first thing that we're working towards, we would like to have a low-rodgers, lower-end
little entry that will find us even a little bit because we're not reaching that free-take-home
yet.
But that's what we're working towards.
Maintaining nipples as the fourth through sixth-grade center.
In the future, we would like to be able to turn our risk-of-pampus into our Miami Innovation
Center.
We currently have our Miami Innovation Center that's focusing on our alternative end-students,
communities, where our kids, we'd be able to have our adult, our alternative end-students
here but then also thinking about how can we provide STEM opportunities in business opportunities
in a space that can become something that's more than what we have currently.
And then we want to look at developing a multi-purpose facility for Maintaining your
high-end high school.
We're already thinking about how we can support our wrestling and our cheer teams, but it needs
to go beyond that.
How can we engage our performing arts community, how can we engage all of our athletic opportunities
and make sure that we're providing an appropriate space for those students to be able to participate.
And we need it goals that we have with this bond, safety and security, infrastructure, and
improved learning environments.
But it's at low-rotters.
Many of you know that prior to the high school-on being passed, and all of the low-rotters, that
came from the need for updates for fire.
That building was no longer going to meet fire code.
We put a forward to do the updates to be able to meet that code, and no longer meds, ADA compliance.
So we can forward to go in and make those updates.
There were also significant mold issues.
So when they looked at how much it would cost to renovate that space at the time, it was more
cost effective to move the middle school, the high school, and build the new high school.
So, but when this happened, it was...
We, you see this grassy area out here, this was re-established to be able to build back for the future.
So this is part of that long-term plan that the district has had to be able to expand building at this site.
So we'd like to with this one to be able to bring our first food dirt great center in this location.
Nibbles of our elementary, we're just wanting to do some basic things there.
So with the previous bond we added on our sixth grade lean, which has a storm shelter, and it's fantastic.
The teachers love it in that space, but in need existing part of the building, it was established in about 1966.
I believe it's the date that I've been given, and the restrooms have not been updated since that time.
So we're dealing with outdated plumbing, it just does not hold up to what we needed to hold up to anymore.
We're also looking at teacher restrooms.
I don't know if you saw one of our videos, but we had a teacher that she's talking about in this situation.
You go in the teacher restroom, and your shoulders are touching the walls, and they overflow, and it's a problem.
And if we want quality staff to come into our district, we have to be able to provide them with basic facilities.
That's the basic eat.
We're also looking at how do we improve our age practices.
So one thing I didn't know, whenever I stepped into this role, is the age of our age practice units.
They are, we have 17 units on that building that are 17 years old.
That's not sustainable because they will last, we're lucky that they've watched it 17 years.
So how can we replace those now, and then develop a plan so that we're not in this situation and the future?
How can we have some sustainability so we can do those updates there?
And then you'll see this, this bill counts.
I talked to you a little bit about before.
Our all-ted students currently go to our move Roger Center, which is great.
They have a great program that's out there.
But what we'd like to do, because they are high school age students, and it's just not going to be appropriate to have high school level students and with first three third grade students.
So we'd like to take this building that has a great structure, and it's really like an open floor plan whenever you get in there.
We'd like to take that and redo that floor plan, do some outside, cosmetic prepares, so that way it looks like an inviting place that you want to go to school.
We'll have our all set out in this building for the time being until we've this bond.
That but here is these are the restrooms for the students that would be updated here.
And then we would do some changes here for teacher restrooms.
So we can improve those things, and then also the age gap.
So that's hitting that efficiency.
Here's our plan for our little Rogers-Lore elementary.
So we went up there, what's existing?
We have some really good solid pieces
within this building already, and we need to make some updates.
Electrical, given cabinetry, things like that,
to make those mushrooms better.
But then we would add 16 additional mushrooms
in some playground updates.
The biggest thing about those 16 additional mushrooms
is in that wing.
We would be able to develop the storm shelter.
So that would give us a storm shelter for first through 12th grade
within our nursery.
Now, something we don't have currently.
Oh, our students at Roosevelt, Washington, and Wilson,
whenever there's a storm, they go into the hallway,
because all of our exterior walls at Washington
and that Wilson is basically glass.
There's windows, and then you can bottom,
it's called spin rule.
So it's another type of glass material.
So we can't leave them in classrooms.
We have to bring them to the hallway,
and we go into restrooms.
So this is for our little needs to be able to.
And it's very, we don't want to have to also allow early either.
We want parents to be able to say,
I think they're safe when they're at school.
I know that they're in a shelter.
For my oldest two, they're both in the junior high and high school.
I know something happens.
They have a safe place to go, and that's why I want for all.
So other things here that would happen,
we would have some each-back updates on the existing part of the building
plus adding new in that new addition.
We would have some updates in the restroom,
and some room replacements, and I have some pictures
to be able to show you.
So this building actually, okay, we need to turn this,
but my slide didn't work quite that,
but it actually goes this other direction,
and it's directly facing nipples.
So this is the entryway that would be directly facing nipples.
This in the purple is existing building.
So this is just where we would do some renovations.
It's made this up on office, up to these classrooms.
We have a place for art, music, and library,
so they're not having to do a process street.
It leaves the gymnasium because you never ever want to get rid of a gymnasium.
We want to do updates, we want to keep it.
You'll see this little guideline here.
We already have the infrastructure to be able to add a curtain,
so you can have two EE spaces going up the time.
It's just a matter of purchasing the curtain.
So we would have that there.
These are all just basic updates,
and then when we get into this section,
this is the new building, the new classrooms.
You can see this area here, is where we would put our swarms shelter.
So we will have to think through which students will be housed in this part of the building.
My thought is that we're having first-to-third grade,
we're playing first-grade classrooms here,
so that we are not having a room.
But this is that swarms shelter.
Now you'll see this great area,
when we talk about that long range plan,
that's where we're talking about adding pretty faint interbarten in the future.
to showing you the parts that would be different from Facebook, so it's not that it's
a whole different placement over the entire building, it's just in these sections.
This is the cafeteria area, so these are the places that we need to have a space, and
so that way when students are coming in, they're getting off the bus, and those students are
going this direction.
We'll order students, we're going the other way, but we're all in one central location.
Here is what session you'll see the playground, we would tough that back, and you'll notice
that kind of made it use, they're awake from the road, those, but they're not full,
last one does that enough to be able to get some sunlight, so it's no teachers know what's
going on outside, but it's still high enough to wear it's not safety comes out.
So this is our area, this will rotters, so that entrance front entrance to Middles, for
two will rotters is right here, front entrance to Middles would be here, we would like to have
happen, is put some gates at the end of both of these roads, so that way the only traffic that's
coming through this is bus traffic, so that's only happening in the morning when kids are getting
dropped off in the afternoon when they're exiting out, this is where the addition would be, here is
that idea of where the playground would be, and we're already thinking about what this future
drop off, let me say that is located up here, that is property of J public schools, and we don't
have any control over what that building is like, with that facility, but we do have those
head students come over and use our storm shelter that is over at Middles, all right, so
some, it would be safe rooms for our first through 12th rain, and getting us closer to our 2036-2037
goal that having all pre-K through 6th rain on one campus, and we're going to be able to approve our facilities
with the efficiency doing those updates, it's going to help us on some efficiency costs, energy costs, it will
help improve our transportation because we have fewer drop off links, and we'll be able to streamline,
I don't know if you are aware, but it's-
So how many of you are drop-off points? Is it when you look at that bus right here?
Can you drive the bus? He's drop-off bus.
Well, then we're in the van.
I'm going to make calling you.
It will also help us with staff elaboration to this right now.
We have teachers that are different campuses and it's a one-word-doing-one-staff-din service
but you just can't collaborate at the level that you need to use.
If we're not all coming together at one place.
So I think that will help with that as well.
Hopefully this just utilized our staff in a better way.
How can we be more efficient with the people's paid off?
School districts can issue new bonds for capital projects while maintaining the current tax rate.
So basically what that means is we have bonds for our SVT or map.
You might want to issue, you have bond issue to add a new office and library
at levels. So those bonds issues have rolled off and they're giving us space to be able to do
this bond without increasing taxes.
That way, we want to get in that cycle to where we're not having to come to taxpayers and asking
them to pay more taxes. We're just able to continue to keep these bond rolling,
continue those improvements. But as long as we keep in that cycle, then we won't have to
ask taxpayer to pay increase property tax.
So here are some other schools that will not be something that we're going to be
but these are some of the schools that in just the last few years who have passed
no tax in three bond issues. It really goes back to that.
This was 7 million bond. If the boat is October 14, you can get out and
vote early on October 9 and October 10.
What the timeline looks like right now, if this were to pass, we would have our first round of
bond proceeds in December to January.
the project that Nicholson, so get those restrooms updated, get them the attractiveness
for places about where they're ready to roll with full starts at the beginning of the
year.
And then with low Rogers, because of how that structure we can start working on, we can start
working on a new part and the hard on the fieldhouse and move those students, the fieldhouse
and then complete the project once we've moved the other students or the fieldhouse.
But we're looking at a total of a whole of the completion by the summer of what you see on
here.
The website, this is our one website, it has frequently asked questions, some of our videos,
really anything that you'd like to see about the ones, you can go to the website.
I have to say as a former MPS employee at Washington to see these updates and to see
the implementation of the long-term plan is such a relief because at Washington, like she
had said, there's no storm shelters, like we had a tornado, we had to go to hallways in
your, like where my group was, was right by the front door and it's just praying that those
doors don't fly open, and so to see the safety measures that you guys are taking, and to also
get those teachers together, that was a big thing for me was we were so disconnected from
campus to campus, and so it made it extremely difficult to make sure that you were doing
your job correctly because of that.
So to see all of this come together and to become more cohesive is amazing, it might
have been from educators perspective.
So good job with me.
So I have a question, this came from a citizen to me, I didn't know the answer, so I'll ask.
The proposed site for little Rogers, just a new building, the ground there, any EPA, or environmental
issues, the task is, we have gone through, I have gone, death through, multiple, gone through,
multiple, finally just, this is report, my understanding, are basically an enterracable level,
so we don't feel like there's any environmental concerns that we have at this time.
Those reports appear to be that would not be an issue for us to prohibit us from building
at this site.
Thank you.
Anything else for Jill?
Thank you so much.
Happy birthday.
Tyler, we're supposed to bring Count K, so he forgot.
I don't know, I didn't know that anymore.
Oh.
Thank you.
You just.
Yes, goodbye.
She's got it.
You too.
All right.
I'm seeing update from the friends of the common regard
in the newly published book on the comb theater
and the opening of their new shop on court.
Channeth and Carol, our sharing account.
She's not the channeth and all this.
Hi.
Mayor Parker.
Yes.
I'm Carol White.
I'm the president of the Friends of the Coleman.
And with me tonight is Sharon Graham, who is our treasurer.
We've come to tell you some exciting news.
And we owe a big thank you to the Miami City Council
and to MDRA for giving us the opportunity to rent the office space
at 103 and 1 half North Main Street, which is the small shop
immediately north of the Coleman theater.
It's part of the Coleman theater complex.
Come October 21st.
We are going to have a soft opening that coincides with my
main streets, sip and shop.
As we open our gift shop to the public.
We're working every day to get ready.
And I want to tell you that Sunday, our volunteers painted the
interior of the building.
And today, with Sharon's help, the floor was clean and a pretty
rug has been laid.
Before Friday, we'll have our showcases in place.
And our chandeliers put up.
So it's going to look like the same kind of motif
that you'd see in the Coleman theater.
It's going to just sort of be an extension of that environment.
We are very happy and very optimistic about the future.
The Friends of the Coleman is a nonprofit organization.
And all of the money that we bring in goes back to the theater.
So Sharon's going to tell you something else that's wonderful
that's happening.
There's hardly a week that goes by.
Well, I know there's not a week that's hardly a day that goes by.
That tours, when they come to the Coleman, have not asked if we had a book
that they could take home with them to tell the story of the Coleman theater.
So what you have before you today is our answer to that question.
About 25 years ago, Robert Wyatt.
who is from Miami, he has a publisher in New York that I see people nodding in New York, wrote
a history of the comment. And so we used that as a starting point. And we have worked
for the past five years to develop the literacy before you. We were very, very blessed.
We had four members of the original friends of the comment, who are on our committee, Jane
Lawsford, Nancy G, Charlene Ligo, and Sally Rollins. And we couldn't put all of their stories
in the book for many reasons. But if you ever want to know anything about the comment
theater and the renovation that has occurred since the Coleman Family David to the
city of Miami, talk to one of those ladies. If it's not in our book, they will tell you about
it and they know about it. Just to give you a sample of what's in there, were you all aware
of that the grand chandelier that hangs in the theater was found in the horse farm at
the Coleman Mansion. It had been trumbled by horses. There was no glass in it. It was just a
metal frame. And all the work that went in to get to be the beauty that you see in there today
is told in our book. The world's third organ was sold out of the theater. And then sold several
more times. It took a lot of searching. I found it in Marles and Texas. And our
warlets are now is the only one that was made in 1928 that is still in its original menu. So again,
something for the city to be very, very proud of. The chandelier, when you enter the ballroom
on the new part, you look at, that's a $38,000 chandelier. And Sally Rollins, one of the
friends of the Coleman, can get in more for Virginia to donate that. So that's just a few of the
stories that you're going to see in the book. We worked with a publishing happening called Donning,
on a Brookfield, Missouri. They had dead other historic buildings. So we chose them to be
our publisher. We worked very closely with their designer and their editor. So we're very proud
of the book. And Carol said every dollar comes back from the book. We'll go back and shoot the theater
into city property with the opportunity. We hope you'll come on the 21st and we hope you'll
like it. I don't like the house. I'm going to say I already have a book.
I'm glad. I'm glad you put pictures in there for novel. Yes, there are over a hundred pictures.
That's good to know. Thank you for letting us go. Thank you. Thank you for your commitment.
to that. What we call the Jewel of Miami, too.
We appreciate that.
So we're excited about the gift shop, too.
We can't wait for you to get to do with it.
It's going to be another place for people to stop.
And we're going to get a lot of more of our species.
We appreciate the gift.
So it's with bears in this stream.
All right, number five, discussion.
A possible action on a city-coin list.
Let's do a proof.
All right.
James Agnacars, I.
Parker.
Five.
Five minutes from the September 16th.
Reg room.
Motion to proceed.
There's also.
He's at.
Charlie.
Hi, Robert.
Hi.
Charlie.
Parker.
Hi.
Thank you, Council for reviewing this this is just a continuation of the growth of our partnership with our tribal partners within the region and to make the process of long forcement and community service smoother with less direction that you have to go every time you have an issue within the tribal lands.
So it's also consistent with the one we just signed with Ottawa as well.
Thank you.
Good.
Bars.
Hi.
Jones.
He steps.
All right.
Thank you.
He proposed ordinance to allow council members to carry bar arms and city council.
I don't know if that's me, but I'm sure there's going to be questions.
I'm going to ask you to draft if we can draft up a and ordinance license for students to use legislation that will pass in May.
That said that we could do that.
So here we are.
We haven't proposed ordinance to allow city council members in certain designated employee to carry bar arms for students.
Any questions?
What certain employees are outside of the council members going to be?
Where's that head?
The judge comes to mind.
He's sitting there.
Are you getting the thumbs up?
I'm getting a big big big carry again.
I don't know.
I think the prosecutor has always been allowed to.
There's a provision to allow prosecutor to.
That's carry.
It's essentially says that whatever the statute allows, we want it.
Councillor Cousinneg Chair.
Chair.
last.
Thank you, Missy.
Thank you, missy.
Ordinary Point.
I'm from the 2025 Ambassador in my resolution in 1924.
I'm from the 2020 F-1926 and 257.
I'm from the I'm from the I'm from the I'm from the I'm from the I'm from the I'm from Oklahoma.
Presidential single family.
Thank you.
Lieutenant buddy, City is only in planning mission travels.
You know?
So, the up for you is, back to the 20F Northwest,
what's 2PD-6, 2PD-7, Belmont Edition.
So, originally this property was zoned RS5,
residential single family.
Sometime, zoned C5, or a huge lawn of the field.
They wish to resound, and it does fit the square footage.
So, the reason I urge that, and I urge that, and I urge that,
by the information that this is.
Thank you.
This is a good thing, because that being zoned for C5,
for all these years, which is a journal commercial.
We would have had a hard time keeping somebody from putting just that,
some type of business in it, which could have been schoolwork.
It could have went south, pretty quick.
If you wanted to adopt something in there.
So, that's what we're proposing, and there's not it.
The university clause, you'll take a bit of the,
as we'll encourage this stuff like that.
So, the word my recommendation is to,
you don't have a reason that to see this.
I know.
Most of it.
I'll say thank you.
Hi.
James.
I'm six.
Discussion items.
Item A.
right now. So I bring before you the proposed 2026 and 10-year calendar for you all to look
at and ask questions. Again, we are embellishing on the things that we normally do, events that
we have in Miami, as well as adding to our calendar for next year. So I'm just going to highlight
a few things, December of 2025. We have all of our normal quote unquote Mayor's Christmas tree
lighting, the parade. And we're going to add a ball drop on Main Street on New Year's Eve from
10 p.m. to Midnight. There is an unbeknownst fifth ball that Cody Allen owns that was
mistrilled. So we are going to sparkle it up and be able to hang it and down by the Mayor's Christmas
tree. We're going to count and have it come down and light up 2026 on the road and hopefully a
few fireworks and have food trucks and just welcome in our 2026 year on the route. My vision is that
when the snowflakes come down, off the Main Street, our Centennial Banners will go up and we'll be there
for the year. February March and April, we have several things going on. Most of them are things
that would happen, but the Coleman MLT is doing a Route 66 musical, which is very cool. It will be for
two weekends that weekend. And then we have our mural fest, which is returning to Miami this year
and I'll have a Route 66 theme. And the dobson is doing several historical displays throughout the year
having to do with USA to 50 and the Centennial. May brings us, we're going to celebrate our graduating
seniors by having posters made with their name, their co-curricular activities and then parents can
buy them for a small amount of money and we will put them up in businesses up and down Main Street and
when Grandma comes to town. Sally comes to town. Hi, my picture is on Main Street. Would you go,
let's go to the business and let's see it. So we're going to celebrate our seniors the entire month of May.
Again, there's a dobson, USA 250, July 3 September display. Take you to September. We have a really, really
cool event that we've planned. It's called the Route 66 Tri-City Cruise Night. That's going to involve
Mayama, Kwappa, and Commerce. Each city from 2 to 5 pm will be responsible for their own food trucks,
their own entertainment, putting together their own car show and then from 5 to 10, that'll be the cruise and
they will cruise from Mayama all the way to Kwappa and turn around and come back so that's going to be about 20 miles
that they can visit other towns and we'll have a cruise night that evening.
November brings a public school Mayama.
School's Route 66 Art Show and that will be every child in the school district and we will have an art display at the civic center
There's not gonna be any prizes. We're just gonna celebrate the work and the creativity of
our students
On November 10, we're going to have Route 66 largest birthday cake and have a birthday celebration for the root the actual birthday is on November 11
But that is also a holiday. So we're gonna celebrate the day before
I've been in conversation with Terran big goods and he
He and I together are gonna create a five by six great big shield
Centennial cake. Then we have the holiday market giving tree and then we're back to December of 26 with a
Maristory lighting and the Christmas parade
So we have a full-year plan and that's not anything we did the Main Street calendar this morning
So the Main Street calendar will also be coming out also
Questions and we talked about it when we talked about the logos, but that interactive
QR-skating mapping. Is that a thing it's working on that. Yes. Yeah, once we get our spaces
Once we yeah, yeah, yeah, Sean and I actually talked about that today
Okay, so about the
Oh, oh, so just having the follow-up, we're gonna have a sit and chop the main from other day. Just have the phone
Think of the Maya, but we're gonna dress up as seniors
Senior read us
I'll also tell you and Mart in March. We're gonna look for bless of Marker and all of the stores
Right we're gonna look
We're gonna we're gonna come up with something in March
We're gonna find bless O Parker in the stores and then you'll get a prize what if you go to the stores and look around
You all have a question about the Centennial
Seven other new business if any which business is post-natured
Misty has one thing on the hope we were in fall soon
laying there and yet another opioid loss is that Chief Sixman was been in with the document
for it today and I know that they needed to be signed by tomorrow.
So I was in the document that started to review them and how does that there were multiple
other documents, uh, records that we didn't have.
So Chief Sixman got started to collect those documents and those are some 500 pages of documents
that need to be reviewed by tomorrow for me to make a legal recommendation whether or not
is okay to sign off on them.
And I don't know that it will be done.
I will do my best tonight, but here's the problem.
The produce of the opioid settlement long-save up on its notice when we face the deadlines
for that part of it has been extended, but in reviewing that settlement agreement, first
of all I know that said it was an attachment to a bankruptcy filing and then I started
to notice that there are very specific statements about the state of Oklahoma within that.
One, for instance, that Oklahoma's subdivision means subdivision within Oklahoma
as specified and exhibit age, which we did not have, it was listed nowhere in any of the websites,
I called, I law your proposal on the city and was not very nice and at 443, sincey that,
the things we wanted to happen is that Oklahoma was the only thing to do for use for arms,
by or to do their filing bankruptcy.
So the state of Oklahoma did, and wrote that in the bankruptcy, what happened?
One, two hundred and fifty five million dollars.
After the bankruptcy, the state of Oklahoma is having 12.5 million dollars set aside for students
to do that judgment, and then there is an additional 30,000 dollars, which I think is from
the other post bankruptcy, what again, that they were supposed to as the helping column.
What are they calling them?
The secondary manufacturer.
Yeah, that's all they're calling.
of these documents, but I doubt that I will be able to anticipate and without committee
round practice days, but there is absolutely nothing in these documents that will not
hurt the city. One individual who works for one of the law firms, who represents some
of the House, said, well, those self and agreements that you are signing off saying that
you've reviewed, they might have been reviewed by the Lawyers who wrote them, the Lawyers
that you worked for, but there is no real need to review them. I said, yeah, it
goes well, you're going to find some of the stating that they were looking out for the
best interest of my town when they wrote them, and accept responsibility and liability,
and that would be great, but I guess they're not going to do that. So this is just so that
everyone is on the same page. Additionally, I'm just going to pick in the behalf of what
have to vote to participate in this, or not to participate in it, if the Council chooses to
participate, I would recommend that you vote to participate in being a legal review.
And it must be what you want them to authorize me to sign it then, as well, so we wouldn't be.
I mean, the thing is, it's all in front of our damnedest we do and damnedest we don't, because
if we don't participate, then we're close. Very likely, we would be able to be able to obtain the grant
and money that will be available to the town through the trucks that have been formed on this deep
and to think we're all fixed. The good sign of that is, you're really, I mean, you take a gamble if
you are going to sign off on something, because what I do that we're finding on on is that we have
reviewed all of the settlement agreements, and that we know the terms of them and the great to be bailed by.
I think most of that entails that we, we understand that we are formal and in the future right
to do on the, you know, in the future, whether we know about it or not, but I can't say for sure
that that's all that we're going to agree with. It's a different one than the last grant.
It's a different, you know, this is more affiliated with the opioid settlement money that we got,
then it is with the grant. That's a separate planning source.
The way I was explained to me this morning when I talked to the AG's office was that this money will be put into trust
to then fund secondary grants once all the money comes in and it's ran in process.
So it doesn't have anything to do with the grant that we've been awarded to.
So besides the grant, like the last settlement that we have, like the city of Miami,
I get so much money every year for the next 20 years.
And one of the other things that this is supposed to do is open up some of that money
because it realized how restricted that our agreement was that we can't spend it on anything.
So part of that is you also open some of that house.
You can.
My understanding is that the reason that they are pushing them all of the town in my can of the homeless,
who are eligible to sign off on this, is that it's been everything.
These signs off were increased, but the amount has been that we're going to get.
But I got to call about it today as well.
I don't want to call teeth.
He don't want to call, but I guess they had a bad contact number.
And we're sending it to someone else.
From what the AG's office explained was they use a third party vendor to send the impression out.
And whoever they were sending it to was not the accurate listing for the city of Miami.
I, not to argue with the AG's office, but okay.
We actually received notice on this on Friday, but nobody knew what it was.
And so yesterday we had training today, we came in.
Who's supposed to be doing this?
Nobody knew.
So that's why called the AG's office and I got a mystery and we started working on it.
I got a goal.
And there's a larger one with Purdue, which was a larger drug manufacturing company, but it's not due to the end of this month.
So not to be confused with the ones that we already have.
And this one and then larger.
For millions, as well, quite five million.
And then all of the other ones are the, I've heard the number of 13 million somewhere.
That the secondary manufacturers have an aggregate of 13.
It's the way it was applied to me.
But I'm very, very far above, though.
I'm maybe completely off.
Each one of the secondary manufacturers has a set of them out when you agree with that.
They have to have to fund where they have to give us, or supply to the state.
I'll ask, but to the state.
Narcan at their price.
So any quailant to whatever that money is would be to offset whatever it is, as I think the numbers higher than
13 million from the documents that I read.
Like each one of them is looking at 13 to 75 million from the different summons that I read.
But that can be offset by doing it through Narcan.
Agreed.
Pond.
There might be good promotion.
Yes.
If I make a motion, we approve.
Pendingly overview and authorize the manager is Daisy B.
Decide.
Second.
A parker?
A parker.
A simple.
A June.
What are you supposed to know?
Um, I saw the poster for the karaoke fundraiser.
Super high.
Just super low.
Oh, can I park a game?
Jump.
No, I was just getting off the lift.
I have a pants on the day when the different mood.
Oh, you're your driver.
No, I'm wearing shorts just for the record.
I went in the lounge.
Not in a medical community announcements.
about the street people and they're being kids with them on the street.
There's no kids, right?
As a just time possibly.
We still haven't got to do it for me.
Absolutely.
So if there is, would you please, because that's really kind of concerning to me up,
that might the dirt could be a natural...
live in on the street. It's unacceptable for anybody to be living on the street in my mind.
But for kids to be on the street.
Is there any kind of zoning issues or anything?
Travis, does that mean only hold up I would think?
So I would say it probably won't work with Travis,
what the zoning is and if it needs to change,
it has to go to zoning board.
But it's a charity that has the care for really cool advance.
It was really cool.
At the same point when he's coming in,
probably the most active we are.
Our airport's had one day.
Maybe every around 30 people.
But it's cool to be at.
So I thought Travis, I'd like to see it happen every year.
People think me and you seem to enjoy it.
There's a lot of people who mess with me saying,
man, what should I know about that?
I've been there.
I don't know how you didn't know about it.
It was all over the place.
But I think the turnout might get,
just like in the other, man, we do the first one.
People don't realize what it is and it grows in there.
But I don't travel so I can see one in the spring,
maybe like a burgers and brawls or something like that.
But we had, we had people flying from Guthrie,
from the Paris, in Guthrie, Wagner, Kansas,
from Missouri.
There was some some from Arkansas.
So cool place.
There was one that I could land on.
Water, water, water.
Yeah, it was cool.
So it's never been mine before.
Because mine was born that big hit.
It was a gold hit.
Let us show off the new terminal a little bit and people are really impressed.
The people require more.
And I don't know, I've never been to Clairemore's Airports, but we're really impressed with our car.
So pretty cool. Pretty cool, man.
So we can keep them the same day. We had the BBQ cook-off competition and car show.
That's very grounds. Another good event.
Had a big time for a discussion from the BBQ teams.
Council showed up at the time.
About 30.
About 90 breakfast breads.
In the dark.
With some staff.
Some seats. That's there too.
We start breakfast all the teams there.
And pretty cool. Pretty cool.
Early.
I've got a book.
My daughter's birthday.
All right.
But it was a good school dance.
And it's a lot for one day.
But I think there's a lot of activity.
And when I was at the barbecue place.
People were asking, why are all these planes flying over?
Which makes me feel good.
Because it was a school to see that.
Then we were going to stop standing there and help them give out the trophies.
You started saying to fly out.
So it was a pretty cool day in my own event.
But I appreciate all the things you staff.
That could have never happened without all of you.
So we appreciate all of you for doing that.
Thanks for cracking eggs, Molly.
She's back there.
Yeah.
Molly showed up late.
But she showed up.
Kevin brought her coffee.
I like it.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm Tia.
You've got something for a meal.
Never Tia.
I'm a city manager.
A couple things.
Four things actually.
So as everybody knows, we have our annual seniors meeting coming up.
And so we have some bad news on that.
So Carla has recently informed us that she is going to
step down or not be re-appointed to the senior citizens board.
So remember the bylaws.
So we have to have a council member on the board.
So I don't know if we want to look at putting someone on there in the future.
This will be an engine on him in the future or just update the bylaws to reflect something else.
I'm just letting it be announced.
But the huge she used to feel obviously with.
I think.
I don't know.
So.
I want to say something on that.
You know, we changed the word.
Are artists aware?
As consumers needed to be in the Thompson stuff.
And there was a reason why.
Because we've kind of had some words that were about.
We didn't know what was going on.
And we were getting blogged side of bottom stuff.
So we put it where we had a council member on there.
Well.
I think most were a staffs under control.
Now.
Our council member.
We've reached pretty thin.
You know a lot of such jobs and businesses and grandkids.
And so I think we're made trying to change that.
where instead of the council member on everyone,
we're going to be able to do a city staff member.
Well, I think one of the things too is that in crossing over and working so directly with the city.
It's honestly caused as conflict with Tyler.
And so closely with his staff, the steps should probably gone the time.
But you think you have an control because staff should have gone through Tyler just causing a lot more.
I think the ones that really brought a lot of this delight with their work,
but therefore more than it was a show's knuckle.
And I don't know about health or prisoners at it.
But anyway, I think for the most part we're going to do that.
You got it all lined out, look at it.
But they want to think we'll punch our work on.
Because I mean, we've got to boys and we can do that.
We don't need to be now working on everything.
And I'm positive news. We have the bull bash Saturday, so that'll be a really cool event.
I'll be right there.
And then we have the sip and shop October 21st, 4 to 7.
Do we have the holiday market number 14th through N15.
So that'll be really cool.
So we have some really cool events downtown going on.
So yeah, Christmas.
There's very, very time.
You're very, very, very different.
I think that's what it's like.
You're going to make it all nice this year.
Yeah.
You can do it.
I know you've never been there before.
That's all I have.
All right.
Thank you.
Hi.